(
"ai_sub_version": "3.0.3",
"generated_at": "2026-07-02T10:56:40.691329",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 16,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
「AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover」平成 vs 令和 アニソン歌合戦
[AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover: Heisei vs. Reiwa Anisong Battle]
AZKi 8th Birthday Live
AZKi
AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover 平成 vs 令和 アニソン歌合戦
[AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover: Heisei vs. Reiwa Anisong Battle]
IRyS / 音乃瀬奏
[IRyS / Kanade Otonose]
みんなこんあずきー！
Hi, everyone! Kon'AZKi!
今日は、AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover
Today is the AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover,
平成・令和 アニソン歌合戦へお越しいただきありがとうございます！
thank you so much for coming to the Heisei vs. Reiwa Anime Song Battle!
今回は、平成赤チームと令和青チームの2チームに分かれて
This time, we are divided into two teams: the Heisei Red Team and the Reiwa Blue Team...
アニソンで歌合戦をやっていきます！
...and we'll be having a singing battle with anime songs!
今回ゲストのみんなも、それぞれのチームに分かれて参戦してくれます！
All of our guests today will also split up into their respective teams to participate!
ハッシュタグは #AZKi生誕ライブ2026 こちらこちら！
The hashtag is #AZKiSeitanLive2026! It's right here!
で、ぜひですね
And please...
赤チーム、ここが良かったよ！とか
...post things like, "The Red Team was great here!"...
青チーム、ここが美しかったよ！とかですね
...or "The Blue Team was so beautiful here!"
たくさんポストお願いします！
Please post a lot!
そして、サムネイルにも書いてありますが
Also, as written in the thumbnail...
新衣装のお披露目と！
...we will be revealing a new outfit...
重大告知もあるので
...and we also have a major announcement...
楽しみにしててください！
...so please look forward to it!
ということで、みんな盛り上がる準備はいいかー！？
With that said, is everyone ready to get hyped?!
おお！
Oh!
それでは、平成・令和 アニソン歌合戦、開幕です！
Well then, let the Heisei vs. Reiwa Anime Song Battle begin!
まずは平成赤チーム
First up, Heisei Red Team!
IRyS
楽曲は
The song is...
アニメ『新世紀エヴァンゲリオン』より、すべての始まりとなる一曲
...the song that started it all, from the anime "Neon Genesis Evangelion"...
『残酷な天使のテーゼ』
"A Cruel Angel's Thesis"!
続いて令和青チーム
Next up, Reiwa Blue Team!
音乃瀬奏
Kanade Otonose!
楽曲は
The song is...
『シン・エヴァンゲリオン劇場版』より、すべてを終わりに導く曲
...the song that brings everything to an end, from "Evangelion: 3.0+1.0 Thrice Upon a Time"...
『One Last Kiss』
"One Last Kiss"!
時代を超えて交差する二つのメロディ、二曲続けてどうぞ！
Two melodies crossing over time! Please listen to both songs back-to-back!
残酷な天使のように
Like a cruel angel,
少年よ神話になれ
young boy, become a myth!
蒼い風がいま 胸のドアを叩いても
Even if the blue wind now knocks on your heart's door,
私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
You are just staring at me and smiling.
そっとふれるもの もとめることに夢中で
Absorbed in seeking what you gently touch,
運命さえまだ知らない いたいけな瞳
You don't even know your fate yet, those innocent eyes.
だけどいつか気付くでしょう その背中には
But someday you'll notice that on your back,
遥か未来めざすための 羽根があること
There are wings meant to aim for the distant future.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
A cruel angel's thesis, soon you will fly from the windowsill.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
If you betray your memories with overflowing, hot pathos,
この宇宙を抱いて輝く 少年よ神話になれ
Embrace this universe and shine, young boy, become a myth!
Fariya
Tuse
Sesta
Merna
Fariya
Tuse
ずっと眠ってる 私の愛の揺りかご
Always sleeping, the cradle of my love
あなただけが 夢の使者に 呼ばれる朝がくる
The morning will come when only you are called by the messenger of dreams
細い首筋を 月あかりが映してる
The moonlight reflects on your slender neck
世界中の時を止めて 閉じこめたいけど
I want to stop the time of the whole world and lock it up
もしもふたり逢えたことに 意味があるなら
If there is meaning in the two of us meeting
私はそう 自由を知るためのバイブル
I am, indeed, the bible for knowing freedom
残酷な天使のテーゼ 悲しみがそしてはじまる
Cruel angel's thesis, and then the sadness begins
抱きしめた命のかたち その夢に目覚めたとき
When you wake up from that dream, the shape of the life you embraced
誰よりも光を放つ 少年よ神話になれ
Releases more light than anyone, young boy, become a myth
人は愛をつむぎながら 歴史をつくる
People spin love while creating history
女神なんてなれないまま 私は生きる
I live on without being able to become a goddess
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
Cruel angel's thesis, you will eventually fly from the window
ほとばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
If you betray your memories with the hot pathos gushing out
この宇宙を抱いて輝く 少年よ神話になれ
Embrace this universe and shine, young boy, become a myth
初めてのルーブルは なんてことはなかったわ
My first time at the Louvre was no big deal
私だけのモナリザ もうとっくに 出会ってたから
Because I'd already met my own Mona Lisa, long ago
初めて あなたを見た あの日 動き出した歯車
The day I first laid eyes on you, wheels began to turn
止められない 喪失の予感
An unstoppable premonition of loss
もういっぱいあるけど
We already have so many
もう一つ 増やしましょう
But let's add another one
Can you give me one last kiss?
忘れたくないこと
Something I don't want to forget
Oh oh oh oh oh...
忘れたくないこと
Something I don't want to forget
Oh oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
「写真は苦手なんだ」 でもそんなものはいらないわ
"I don't like being photographed," but I don't need such things
あなたが焼きついたまま 私の心のプロジェクター
Your image is burnt forever in my heart's projector screen
寂しくないふりしてた まあ、そんなのお互い様か
I was pretending I wasn't lonely, well, I guess that makes two of us
誰かを求めることは すなわち傷つくことだった
Yearning for someone comes hand in hand with a heartache
Oh, can you give me one last kiss?
燃えるようなキスをしよう
Let's share a kiss as hot as fire
忘れたくても
Even if I wanted to forget
忘れられないほど
So passionately that I can't forget
Oh oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
Oh oh oh oh...
もう分かっているよ
I already know
この世の終わりでも
That whether it's the end of the world...
年をとっても
Or if I grow up to be old...
忘れられない人
Someone I can't forget
Oh oh oh oh...
忘れられない人
Someone I can't forget
Oh oh oh oh...
忘れられない人
Someone I can't forget
I love you more than you'll ever know
Oh oh oh oh...
忘れられない人
Someone I can't forget
Oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
忘れられない人
Someone I can't forget
I love you more than you'll ever know
吹いていった風のあとを
Chasing after the breeze that blew by...
追いかけた眩しい午後
On one dazzling afternoon...
AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSSOVER!
AZKi's 8th Birthday Live: CROSSOVER!
平成 vs 令和 アニソン歌合戦！
Heisei vs. Reiwa Anime Song Battle!
平成 赤チーム 常闇トワ！
Heisei Red Team: Tokoyami Towa!
楽曲は アニメ『けいおん！』より ガールズバンド旋風を巻き起こしたクールなロックナンバー
From the anime "K-On!", the cool rock number that sparked a girls' band sensation:
「Don't say \"lazy\"」！
"Don't say \"lazy\""!
続いて令和 青チーム 響咲リオナ！
Next, Reiwa Blue Team: Hibiki Riona!
楽曲は アニメ『ぼっち・ざ・ろっく！』より 令和のバンドアニメの代表曲
From the anime "Bocchi the Rock!", the representative song of Reiwa band anime:
「星座になれたら」！
"If I Could Be a Constellation"!
時代を超えて響き渡るガールズバンドの系譜
The lineage of girls' bands echoing across eras...
2曲続けてどうぞ！
Please listen to these two songs back-to-back!
Please don't say "you are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because, honestly, it's crazy
白鳥たちはそう
Swans are like that
見えないとこでバタ足するんです
They paddle furiously out of sight
本能に忠実・忠実
Obedient and faithful to instinct
翻弄も重々承知
Fully aware of being toyed with too
前途洋々だし…
The future is bright, after all...
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
So, sometimes, we take a break
この目でしっかり見定めて
Fix your gaze with these eyes
行き先地図上マークして
And mark your destination on the map
近道あればそれが王道
If there's a shortcut, it's the royal road
はしょれる翼もあれば上等
And if you have wings to fly, that's top-notch
ヤバ 爪割れたグルーで補修した
Oh no, my nail broke, I fixed it with glue
それだけでなんか達成感
Just that gives me a sense of accomplishment
大事なのは自分かわいがること
What's important is to love yourself
自分を愛さなきゃ他人も愛せない
If you don't love yourself, you can't love others
Please don't say "you are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because, honestly, it's crazy
能ある鷹はそう
Hawks with talent are like that
見えないとこにピック隠すんです
They hide their picks out of sight
想像に一生懸命
Giving everything to imagination
現実は絶体絶命
Reality is in a desperate situation
発展途中だし…
Still a work in progress...
だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
So, unexpectedly, the pitch goes off...
That is why I suddenly go off-pitch
その目に映らないだけだってやる気はメーター振り切って
Even if you can't see it, my motivation's off the charts
いつでも全力で夢見て その分全力で眠って
I always dream with all my might, and sleep just as hard to make up for it
ヤリ ちょい痩せた 調子づいて喰った
Oh, look, I lost a little weight! So I ate a bunch on impulse
それだけでなんで？敗北感
Why do I feel such defeat from just that?
すかさずに目標 下方修正して
I immediately lower my goals
柔軟に臨機応変 七変化が勝ち
Flexibility and adaptability, being versatile is the key to winning
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because actually, I'm crazy
孔雀たちはそう
Peacocks are just like that
ここぞというとき美を魅せるんです
They only show off their beauty when it counts
五臓六腑 満身邁進
Heart and soul, giving it my all
願望は痩身麗人
My desire is to be a slender beauty
誘惑多発だし…
There are so many temptations, after all...
だからやけに意志砕けちゃうんです
That's why my willpower crumbles so easily
ヤバ まさか赤点！？いや ギリクリア！
Oh no, did I fail?! No, I barely passed!
それだけでなんて全能感
Why do I feel so omnipotent from just that?
大事なのは自分認めてくこと
The important thing is to accept yourself
自分を許さなきゃ他人（ひと）も許せない
If you don't forgive yourself, you can't forgive others
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because actually, I'm crazy
白鳥たちはそう
Swans are just like that
見えないとこでバタ足するんです
They are paddling furiously where you can't see
本能に従順忠実
Loyal and faithful to my instincts
翻弄も重々承知
Fully aware of being played with
前途洋々だし…
My future is bright, after all...
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
That's why I sometimes take a break
星座になれたら
If I Could Be A Constellation
もうすぐ時計は6時
The clock will soon strike six
もうそこに一番星
The first star is already there
影を踏んで 夜に紛れたくなる帰り道
On my way home, I want to step on my shadow and vanish into the night
どんなに探してみても
No matter how hard I search
一つしかない星
There's only one star
何億光年 離れたところからあんなに輝く
Shining so brightly from billions of light-years away
いいな 君は みんなから愛されて
It's nice, you are loved by everyone
「いいや 僕は ずっと一人きりさ」
"No, I've always been all alone"
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation
星降る夜 一瞬の願い事
On a night of falling stars, a split-second wish
きらめいて ゆらめいて
Twinkling, swaying
震えてるシグナル
A trembling signal
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation
空見上げて 指を差されるような
Looking up at the sky, as if being pointed at
つないだ線 解かないで
Don't untie the connected line
僕がどんなに眩しくても
No matter how dazzling I am
もうすぐ時計は8時
The clock is soon to be 8 o'clock
夜空に満天の星
The night sky is full of stars
何億光年 離れたところにはもうないかもしれない
They might not even exist anymore from billions of light-years away
月が綺麗で
The moon is so beautiful...
泣きそうになるのは
And the reason I feel like crying is
いつの日にか
Because one day
別れが来るから
Our parting will surely come
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation
彗星みたい 流れるひとりごと
A monologue flowing like a comet
消えていく残像は 真夜中のプリズム
The disappearing afterimage is a midnight prism
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation
切なる願い 誰かに届いたかな
I wonder if my earnest wish reached someone
変われるかな 夜の淵を
I wonder if I can change, tracing the edge of the night
なぞるような こんな僕でも
Even a me like this
遥か彼方 僕らは出会ってしまった
Far away, we happened to meet
カルマだから 何度も出会ってしまうよ
Because it's karma, we will meet again and again
雲の隙間で
Through the gaps in the clouds
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation
夜広げて 描こう絵空事
Spreading the night, let's paint our wild dreams
暗闇を 照らすような 満月じゃなくても
Even if it's not a full moon that lights up the darkness
だから集まって星座になりたい
So I want to gather with you and become a constellation
色とりどりの光 放つような
Releasing a light of all sorts of colors
つないだ線 解かないよ
Don't untie the connected line
君がどんなに眩しくても
No matter how dazzling you are
AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSSOVER 平成 vs 令和 アニソン歌合戦！平成・赤チーム...
AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSSOVER: Heisei vs Reiwa Anisong Battle! Red Team representing Heisei...
ロボ子さん！
Roboco-san!
楽曲はアニメ『円盤皇女ワるきゅーレ』より『Agape』。
Her song is 'Agape' from the anime 'UFO Princess Valkyrie'.
続いて令和・青チーム...
Next up, Blue Team representing Reiwa...
水宮枢！
Mizumiya Suu!
楽曲は令和版アニメ『うる星やつら』より『トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ』。
Her song is 'Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous' from the Reiwa version of 'Urusei Yatsura'.
宇宙から届いた2つのラブソング、2曲続けてどうぞ！
Please enjoy these two love songs from space back-to-back!
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
Wherever I am, I can hear you
君がくれる agape
The agape that you give me
力の限り dive!
Dive with all your might!
みつめる 触れ合う その時
Gazing and touching each other, at that very moment...
愛は二人を試している
Love is testing the two of us
Time is now
この世の果てまで
To the ends of this world
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
Wherever you are, I can hear it
君がくれる Agape
The Agape you give me
力の限り Dive!
With all my strength, I'll dive!
信じる 応える その瞬間
Believing, responding, at that moment...
愛が 僕らを ひとつにする
...love makes us one
Time is now
どこまでも生きて
Live on, no matter where
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
Wherever you are, I can hear it
君がくれる Agape
The Agape you give me
力の限り Dive!
With all my strength, I'll dive!
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
Wherever you are, I can hear it
君がくれる Agape
The Agape you give me
力の限り Dive!
With all my strength, I'll dive!
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
Wherever you are, I can hear it
君がくれる Agape
The Agape you give me
力の限り Dive!
With all my strength, I'll dive!
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
Wherever you are, I can hear it
君がくれる Agape
The Agape you give me
力の限り
With all my strength...
Dive!
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中！
Radio waves tempo up, currently highly electrocuted!
あなたにもわすれたいことかなしいこと
Is there something you want to forget, something sad, too?
あるのかしらね
I wonder if you also have them
識らない映画なのに涙をながすのは
Crying over a movie you don't even know...
ドラマチックが足りていないからよ
...is just because you lack drama
そんな愚にも付かないことくだらないこと
You're always thinking about...
考えてばかりね
...foolish, trivial things
雨が上がれば愛もその横顔も誰かのものになるのでしょう
When the rain clears, love and that side profile will belong to someone else, won't they?
嘘っぱちのファンデーションも全部今夜のためよ
All this phony foundation is for tonight
なのに一体全体如何して何故？ 如何して何故？ 何故何故怒ってんの？
But why on earth, why, why? Why, why, are you angry?
不安定なカンテラ何処まで行くの
How far will this unstable lantern go?
あなた一切合切放り去ってもう
You throw it all away and leave
冗談じゃあないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
It's no joke! Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
Even if that time comes, nothing can be done
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
Ambiguous truths just turn into melancholy
あたしをさあ掻き攫って今テイクオンミー
So, whisk me away, take on me now
ちゃんちゃらおかしな法度ばっかで食指がびくともしないわ
It's ridiculous, with all these taboos, my appetite won't be stirred
実態の無い感情放っておいたって
Even if you leave those formless feelings alone
策略なんてありゃあせんのに何故
Even though there are no strategies, why?
ああもう懲り懲りよ あたしの喝となる気質も
Ah, I'm already tired of it, my stimulating temperament
じっと堪えて取り繕ってはとうとう臨界点
Enduring and putting on a front, finally reaching the critical point
年がら年中リップサービス鈍感カマしては辟易
Year-round giving lip service, playing dumb and getting fed up
どんがらがっしゃんフィールガールは涙の目にも鬼
The girl who is a 'feel girl' is a demon even in teary eyes
今や頭の中のミュージックのせいであなたの話は一向に聴き取れない
Now, because of the music in my head, I can't hear your story at all
少しは真当なこと言って
Say something sensible for once
回り出すターンテーブル ねえ全部忘れさせてよ
Spinning turntable, hey, let me forget everything
だけど一体全体如何して何故？ 如何して何故？ 何故何故怒ってんの？
But why on earth, why, why? Why, why, are you angry?
不安定なカンテラ消えない儘ね
An unstable lantern, it won't go out
あなた一口両舌食い違ってもう
You speak with a forked tongue, eating your words
冗談じゃあないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
It's no joke! Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
Even if that time comes, nothing can be done
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
Ambiguous truths just turn into melancholy
あたしを今...
Whisk me away...
冗談じゃあないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
It's no joke! Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
Even if that time comes, nothing can be done
不甲斐ないわ
It's pathetic
感情なんてランドリーで落とすだけ
I'll just wash away these feelings in the laundry
あたしと確かめ合ってイエローマジック
Verify it with me, yellow magic
アイヤイヤ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Ai-ya-ya, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
Even if that time comes, nothing can be done
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
Ambiguous truths just turn into melancholy
あたしをさあ掻き攫って今テイクオンミー
So, whisk me away, take on me now
AZKi 8th Birthday Live「Crossover」平成 vs 令和 アニソン歌合戦
AZKi 8th Birthday Live 'Crossover' Heisei vs Reiwa Anisong Song Battle!
最後はチームみんなで歌い上げます
At the end, everyone in the team will sing together!
平成赤チーム
Heisei Red Team:
アニメ「とある科学の超電磁砲」より、今も愛され続けるアニソンの王道、「only my railgun」
From the anime 'A Certain Scientific Railgun', the classic anisong loved to this day, 'only my railgun'.
続いて令和青チーム
Next up, Reiwa Blue Team:
アニメ「呪術廻戦」より、鮮烈でエモーショナルな青春ソング、「青のすみか」
From the anime 'Jujutsu Kaisen', the vivid and emotional youth song, 'Ao no Sumika'.
ステージでぶつかる電撃と呪力。2曲続けてどうぞ！
Electric shock and cursed energy clashing on stage. Please enjoy both songs in a row!
放て！心に刻んだ夢を 未来さえ置き去りにして
Release! The dream carved into my heart, leaving even the future behind
限界など知らない 意味無い！
I don't know any limits, it's meaningless!
この能力(チカラ)が光散らす その先に遥かな想いを
This power scatters light, with distant thoughts beyond that
歩いてきた この道を 振り返ることしか
If I can only look back at this path I've walked...
出来ないなら... 今ここで全てを壊せる
Then... I can destroy everything right here!
暗闇に堕ちる街並み 人はどこまで立ち向かえるの？
In the streets falling into darkness, how far can people stand up?
加速するその痛みから 誰かをきっと守れるよ
From that accelerating pain, I can surely protect someone!
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way. Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 今すぐ
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way. Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. Right now,
身体中を光の速さで駆け巡った確かな予感
A certain premonition ran through my body at the speed of light!
身体中を 光の速さで
With the speed of light throughout my body...
駆け巡った 確かな予感
An unshakeable premonition ran through me!
掴め！望むものなら残さず
Grab it! Don't leave behind anything you wish for,
輝ける自分らしさで
with a brilliance that is uniquely yours.
信じてるよ あの日の誓いを
I believe in the promise of that day.
この瞳に光る涙
Even the tears that shine in these eyes...
それさえも強さになるから
will become my strength!
立ち止まると 少しだけ
When I stand still, just a little,
感じる切なさに
I feel a slight heartbreak.
戸惑う事
To say that I'm not confused...
無いなんて嘘はつかないよ
would be a lie.
宇宙に舞うコインが描く
A coin dancing in space draws a curve,
放物線が決める運命
creating a parabola that determines our fate.
打ち出した答えが今日も
The answer I shot out today also...
私の胸を駆け巡る
runs through my chest.
Sparkling!
The shiny lights awake true desire
Only my railgun can shoot it 必ず
Only my railgun can shoot it, definitely!
貫いてく 戸惑うことなく
I will pierce through without hesitation,
傷ついても 走り続ける
and keep running even if I get hurt!
狙え！凛と煌く視線は
Aim! The cold and sparkling gaze...
狂い無く闇を切り裂く
cuts through the darkness without fail.
迷いなんて 吹き飛ばせばいい
Just blow away all of your hesitation!
この心が叫ぶ限り
As long as this heart continues to scream,
誰ひとり邪魔などさせない
I won't let anyone get in my way!
儚く舞う 無数の願いは
Countless fleetingly dancing wishes...
この両手に 積もってゆく
are piling up in these hands.
切り裂く闇に 見えてくるのは
What comes into view through the split darkness...
重く深く 切ない記憶
are heavy, deep, and painful memories.
色褪せてく 現実に揺れる
Swaying in a fading reality,
絶望には 負けたくない防に
I don't want to lose to despair.
私が今 私であること素なみぐに
That I am who I am right now...
胸を張って 全て誇れる
is something I can hold my head high and be proud of!
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way
Only my railgun can shoot it 今すぐ
Only my railgun can shoot it, right now!
身体中を 光の速さで
With the speed of light throughout my body,
駆け巡った 確かな予感
an unshakeable premonition ran through me.
放て！心に刻んだ夢を
Let go! Of the dreams engraved in your heart,
未来さえ置き去りにして
leaving even the future behind.
限界など知らない 意味無い！
I don't know limits, it's meaningless!
この能力が光散らす
This power scatters light,
その先に遥かな想いを
sending my distant feelings far beyond.
青のすみか
[Song: Ao no Sumika (Where Our Blue Is)]
どこまでも続くような 青の季節は
The season of blue that seems to last forever...
四つ並ぶ眼の前を 遮るものは何もない
There is nothing blocking the front of our four pairs of eyes.
アスファルト、蝉時雨を反射して
Asphalt reflecting the chorus of cicadas...
きみという沈黙が聞こえなくなる
The silence called 'you' becomes completely inaudible.
この日々が色褪せる
These days are fading away,
僕と違うきみの匂いを知ってしまっても
even if I've come to know your scent that is different from mine.
置き忘れてきた永遠の底に
In the depths of eternity that we left behind,
今でも青が棲んでいる
even now, the blue still dwells there.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, that blue remains so clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も
Any prayer or words,
近づけるのに、届かなかった
although they got us closer, they never reached.
まるで、静かな恋のような
Just like a quiet, peaceful love,
頬を伝った夏のような色のなか
inside a color that resembles summer tracing my cheeks...
きみを呼ぶ言葉が、ずっと喉の奥につかえてる
The words to call out to you are still stuck in the back of my throat.
「また会えるよね」って、声にならない声
'We will meet again, right?' in a voice that doesn't make a sound.
昼下がり、じめつく風の季節は
In the early afternoon, in the season of sticky wind,
想い馳せる、まだ何者でもなかった僕らの肖像
Thinking back, a portrait of us when we were still nobodies.
何もかも分かち合えたはずだった
We should have been able to share everything.
あの日から少しずつ
Since that day, little by little,
君と違う僕という呪いが肥っていく
The curse of me being different from you has grown.
きみの笑顔の奥の憂いを
The sorrow deep within your smile,
見落としたこと、悔やみ尽くして
Having missed it, I regret it endlessly.
徒花と咲いて散っていくきみに
To you, blooming and scattering like a sterile flower,
さよなら
Goodbye.
今でも青が棲んでいる
Even now, the blue still dwells inside.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue remains clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も
No matter what prayer or word,
近づけるのに、届かなかった
Though it got us closer, it never reached.
まるで、静かな恋のような
Just like a quiet love,
頬を伝った夏のような色のなか
Amidst a color like summer running down my cheek.
きみを呪う言葉が
The words that curse you
ずっと喉の奥につかえてる
Are still stuck in the back of my throat.
「また会えるよね」って、声にならない声
A silent voice saying, "We'll meet again, right?"
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のように
Like the grains of stars in an infinitely expanding galaxy,
指の隙間を零れた
They slipped through the cracks of my fingers.
はい！ということで、ここまで一気に
Yes! So, we've brought you up to here
ノーストップでお送りしました！
in one non-stop go!
平成も、令和も、名曲ばかりでしたね！
Whether from Heisei or Reiwa, they were all masterpiece songs, weren't they?
どうでしたか？好きな曲はありましたか？
How was it? Did you have any favorite songs?
そして、みんな、どっちのチームが良かったかな？
And also, everyone, which team do you think was better?
えーとですね、このね、今、後ろのこのハートのステージね、
Well, you see, this stage with the heart behind me now...
はい、こちらのハートに映し出された色で、
Yes, by the color projected onto this heart,
どっちのチームが勝ったのか決まります！
it will decide which team won!
ぜひ、みんなコメントで、どっちが良かったか教えてください！
Please, everyone, tell me in the comments which one you liked!
ええ？「決められない」？
Eh? "You can't decide"?
いやいや、そこはね、ちょっとね、決めて...
No, no, you have to choose...
あ、すごい、この二色にね、分かれておりますけれども、
Ah, wow, it's divided into these two colors,
しっかり決めていただかないと！
but you really have to choose one!
はい、今日はね、あの平成VS令和となっております。
Yes, today is Heisei vs. Reiwa!
はい、ということで、勝ったのは平成・赤チームか、
Alright, so, did the Heisei Red Team win,
それとも、令和・青チームか、
or the Reiwa Blue Team?
一体どっちかな？
Which one could it be?
それじゃあ、いくよ！
Well then, here we go!
さあ、結果はこちら！
Alright, here is the result!
お？
Oh?
え？なんか、紫になっちゃったんですけど！
Eh? Wait, it turned purple!
紫って、紫ってどっちですか？
Purple? Which one is purple?
うーん、もうこれは、あの、赤チームも良かったし、青チームも良かったということで、
Hmm, well, I guess both the Red Team and the Blue Team were great,
すべてフュージョンして紫になってしまったということで、
so they fused together and became purple!
いや、みんな、あのたくさん歌ったし、
So, well, everyone sang so much,
ま、みんな最高だったってことにね、します！
and we'll just say everyone was the absolute best!
いや、なんか、なんかね、みんなのおかげで、あ、なんか、パワーが、
Wow, somehow... somehow, thanks to everyone, I feel like power...
パワーが溜まってきた気がするな！
I feel like power is filling up inside me!
気がする！
I really do feel it!
うふふ、ということで、新衣装です！
Ehehe, and with that, here is my new outfit!
えー、みんなのコメ...
Well, everyone's comm...
なんと、全部、AZKiの魔力になっちゃった！
Wow, everything's turned into AZKi's mana!
見てください、どうですか？
Take a look, how is it?
尻尾、尻尾も生えてるんです。
A tail, I even have a tail now.
ふりふりふりふり、どうですか？
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle. How is it?
はい、ということで、今回は、えー、小悪魔衣装を仕立てていただきました！
Yes! So this time, I had a little devil outfit tailored!
どうでしょうか？どうでしょうか？
What do you think? What do you think?
魔力？魔王？小悪魔です。
Magic power? Demon Lord? No, a little devil.
はい、今回の新衣装はこちらの小悪魔衣装。可愛いでしょ？たくさんスクショも撮ってくださいね！
Yes, my new outfit is this little devil outfit. Cute, right? Please take lots of screenshots!
ということで、この衣装でね、せっかくなので、あの曲を歌っていきたいなと思います！
Since I'm wearing this outfit, I'd love to sing *that* song!
もしかしたらね、小悪魔ですから、この姿なら、魔法とかも使えちゃうんじゃないのかな？
After all, since I'm a little devil, maybe I can even use magic in this form!
ということで、ではですね、次の曲、聴いてください！
So without further ado, please listen to the next song!
召喚！
Summon!
自分の過去に囚われ迷って
Caught in the trap of my own past, I'm lost
そうじゃないよと言い聞かせて 全てを
Just telling myself it's not like that, everything...
自由に操れるかなんて
Will I ever be able to control it freely?
分からないよと空は霞んで 正解はどこ？
I don't know, the sky is hazy. Where is the answer?
僕の手のひらに残る大事なもの
This important thing remains in the palm of my hand
忘れない記憶 何度でも
Unforgettable memories, again and again
君を守り抜くと叫んで
Screaming that I will protect you to the end
巻き戻しの中掴んだ愛はそう
The love I grasped in the rewinding time...
離しはしないから
...I won't ever let go of it
散りばめた想い 今一度きりの願いへ
The scattered thoughts lead to a wish made once more
次への僕に託したよ
I've entrusted it to the next me
いつかの約束 光の道しるべになる
The promise of someday will become a guiding light
誓いをさあ君のため
Now, for you, I make this vow
最期まで
Until the very end
涙さえ力に変えてきっと 描いていた望む未来へ
Changing even tears into strength, to the future we pictured
繋ぐよ
I will connect us
想像を超える事態に狂って
Going crazy over situations beyond imagination
爪を立てては もがき足掻いて心は
Digging in my claws, struggling and scratching, my heart...
人生の過ちをもう何回
...how many times must I repeat the mistakes of my life...
繰り返しては嫌いになって 泣いてても
...and come to hate them, even if I'm crying?
君の憧れは いつも輝いてた
Your longing was always shining
I'll come back
To your future
僕は抗うだろう 運命に
I will resist destiny
Breaking out
Breaking down
諦めちゃいないから
Because I won't give up
結ばれた意思は 独りきりじゃない強さへ
The joined will moves toward a strength that isn't alone
紡いだ糸を手繰り寄せ
Pulling on the spun threads
見つけた瞳は 理想を現実に変える
The eyes I found will change the ideal into reality
世界はそう君のため保存版
The world is indeed for you
最初から
From the very beginning
胸に抱いた思い出とずっと あの日から続く決意で
With the memories in my heart and the resolve from that day
飛べるよ Redo
I can fly, Redo!
AZKiちゃん生誕祭！まだまだ行けますか！？盛り上がっていこう！
AZKi's Birthday Festival! Can you keep going?! Let's get fired up!
君がたとえ僕のこと保存版
Even if you...
忘れても
...forget about me
僕はもう忘れない 誰も傷つけない
I won't ever forget again, and I won't let anyone get hurt
消えそうな過去を 救い出すための時間よ
This is the time to rescue a past that's fading away
ここから
From here...
始まれ
...let it begin!
巡りゆく一瞬を 今一度きりの願いへ
To the revolving moments, to a wish made once more
確かに僕は託された
I have certainly been entrusted with it
いつかの約束 光の道しるべになる
The promise of someday will become a guiding light
誓いをさあ 君のため 最期まで
This oath, for your sake, until the very end
涙さえ力に変えてきっと
Even tears will surely turn into strength
描いていた望む未来へ
To the desired future I was drawing
繋ぐよ
I will connect it
わー！
Wow!
ということで、聞いていただいてありがとうございました！
And with that, thank you so much for listening!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
今日は小悪魔衣装になって 魔法で召喚しちゃいました！
Today, I wore my little devil outfit and summoned you with magic!
召喚されちゃいました！こわづき！
I've been summoned! Ko-AZKi!
わー、ありがとう！
Yay, thank you!
ということでですね、皆さんもご存知だと思いますが
And so, as you all probably know...
アニソン界のエース、鈴木このみさんに異世界転生してもらいました！
I had the ace of the anime song world, Konomi Suzuki, reincarnate into this other world!
召喚されました！
I've been summoned!
お誕生日をね、今日はお祝いしたいなと思ってまいりました
I came here today because I wanted to celebrate your birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much!
ということでですね、一緒に歌った曲は
So, the song we just sang together...
「Re:ゼロから始める異世界生活」第1期OPテーマ「Redo」でした！
...was "Redo", the OP theme for the first season of "Re:Zero"!
いかがでしたでしょうか？
How was it?
ドキドキしたなー
That was so nerve-wracking!
私もめっちゃドキドキした！
I was super nervous, too!
なんか「Redo」を人と歌ったことがあんまりなくって
Actually, I've rarely sung "Redo" with someone else before.
えー！
Really?!
怖い顔をして歌ってないかすごい心配です
So I was really worried if I sang with a scary expression.
貴重な、貴重な経験ありがとうございます！
Thank you for such a precious, precious experience!
あずきちと歌えて楽しかった！
It was so fun singing with AZKi!
あずきちって呼んでくれてるんですよ、みんな！
She calls me AZKichi, everyone!
あずきはね、このみんって呼んでるんですけど
And I call her Konomin!
いや、実はね、出会いのきっかけはですね
Actually, the way we met was...
ずっとあずきは元々大好きなんですけど
I've actually always loved Konomin...
このみんがね、あの...
But Konomin, you see...
「異世界かるてっと」の...
...in "Isekai Quartet"...
そう、そう！「異世界かるてっと3」のエンディングテーマ
Yes, yes! We were making the ending theme for "Isekai Quartet 3"...
「君色僕色」のカルテットバージョンを作ることになりまして
...which was the Quartet version of "Kimiiro Bokuiro"...
その時に、会社のスタッフから...
...and at that time, the staff told me...
「誰か一人好きな人を召喚できる権利を差し上げます」って言われて
"We'll give you the right to summon any one person you like."
えー！
Wow!
「そんな機会あるなら、あずきちにお願いしてみたい！」って、ライブも元々観てたんで
"If I have that chance, I want to ask AZKichi!" since I've watched your live shows.
いいんですか？！
Is that really okay?!
いつかコラボしたいなって気持ちがずっとあったので
I've always hoped to collaborate one day, so...
そこでラブコールをして、叶いまして
...I sent you a love call, and it came true!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
まさかそんなことがありまして、そこからコラボ配信とか
I can't believe that's how it happened! And from there, we had collab streams...
あずきも、このみんのライブ観に行かせてもらったりとか
...and I also got to go see Konomin's live show.
ありがとう
Thank you!
あとはね、ラーメンの...
And also, the ramen...
ラーメンの汁をね、飛ばしました
...splashing the ramen broth!
配信の日にそういう話をしていて
We were talking about that on our stream day...
すぐLINEを交換して
...and immediately exchanged LINE contacts!
すぐラーメンの汁を飛ばして
Then we immediately splashed ramen broth...
汁を飛ばして
...splashed broth...
すぐその後、
...and right after that...
焼肉も行って
...we went to get Yakiniku...
油を飛ばす
...and splashed grease!
飛ばして
...splashed it!
アフタヌーンティーにも行きました
We also went to afternoon tea!
一応オシャレなこともしたし、結構ね
We did do some classy things, too!
そうなんです、よく会ってるよね、最近
Exactly, we've been meeting up a lot lately!
なんと仲良くさせていただいております
We've become really close friends.
濃厚なお付き合いで
A very close relationship...
濃厚なお付き合いをさせてもらっておりまして
Yes, we've been sharing a very close bond...
なんと今日、ついにバーチャル空間に来てくれました！
...and today, she finally came to the virtual space!
初めてです！ありがとう！
It's my first time! Thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
なんて楽しい空間なんだ！
What a fun space this is!
嬉しすぎるー！
I'm so incredibly happy!
なんか、この空間は魔法が使えるって聞いたんですけど、本当ですか？
I heard that you can use magic in this space, is that true?
使っちゃいますか？このみんは一体どんな魔法を...
Shall we use it? Konomin, what kind of magic...
あの、私もフェス繋がり、一つだけ魔法を覚えてきたんですよ
Well, since we're connected through festivals, I learned just one magic spell!
えっ！
Really?!
これだけ使える
Only this one works.
あの、これはでも、みんなと一緒じゃないと完成しない魔法なんで
But, this is a magic spell that won't work unless everyone does it together...
ぜひあずきちへの、ラブを込めて
So, with all your love for AZKichi...
何ですか？！
What is it?!
一緒に歌って、魔法を完成させてください！
...please sing along with us to complete the magic!
せーの！
Ready, go!
ハッピーバースデートゥーユー
Happy birthday to you
すごい炎！
Look at the flames!
ハッピーバースデー ディア あずきちー！
Happy birthday, dear AZKichi!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ハッピーバースデートゥーユー
Happy birthday to you
あずきち仕上げをお願いします！
AZKichi, please do the honors of blowing them out!
仕上げ？はい！
Blow them out? Okay!
ふーっ！
[Blows out the fire]
このみんは炎の使い手でした！
Konomin was a fire wielder!
おめでとうございます！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
まさか歌までプレゼントしていただけるなんて
I can't believe I'd even get a song as a present...
もう、もうここで命尽きても...
I could... I could literally die happy right here...
待って、待って！ダメです、ダメです、ダメです！
Wait, wait! No, no, no, don't say that!
命尽きちゃダメなんです...
You can't die just yet!
実は...
Actually...
書いてあると思うんですけどね、サムネに。
I think it's already written on the thumbnail, though.
二人から、重大告知がございます！
We have a major announcement from the two of us!
やった！
Yay!
なんと！二人のオリジナルコラボ楽曲が出ます！
Believe it or not, we are releasing an original collaboration song!
やったー！嬉しい！
Yay! I'm so happy!
いいんですか？/いいんですか？
Is this really okay? / Is it really okay?
ということで、タイトルは...せーの！
And so, the title is... ready, set, go!
最強未来衝動！
Saikyo Mirai Shodo!
という、何だか強そうなタイトルですね。
That's quite a strong-sounding title, isn't it?
強い曲ですね。/強い曲です。
It's a powerful song. / Yes, a powerful song.
ということで、なんと、今日、初披露させていただきます！
So, believe it or not, we will perform it for the first time today!
頑張ろう！
Let's do our best!
それでは早速、聴いてもらえますか。
Then, without further ado, let's have you listen to it.
はい！はい！
Yes! Yes!
それでは、聴いてください。
Now then, please listen.
最強未来衝動
[Song: Saikyo Mirai Shodo]
だから JUST FLY TO THE STAR
So, JUST FLY TO THE STAR
もっと WOW WOW
More, WOW WOW
世界中で PROUDY GLOW
PROUDLY GLOW in the whole world
存在など 歌い切って無い無い
There's no way I've sung all of our existence away
壊れても 関係ない
Even if it breaks, it doesn't matter
そっと触れるよ 生まれたての星へ
I will touch the newborn star gently
一緒に行こう
Let's go together!
行け！
Go!
ここから
From here...
次元を超えていく
Crossing over dimensions!
超えていく
We will cross over...
歌え！この衝動はきっと
Sing! This impulse is surely...
抱かれて染まって 振り切って
embraced, dyed, and shaken off.
まだ
Still...
ほら
look...
星を締め付ける
tightening around the stars.
君と絡まってみようか
Shall we get entangled with you?
止まらないよ 最強未来衝動
It won't stop, the strongest future impulse!
ただ
Just...
just...
ただ 剥がれ落ちてく
just peeling and falling off.
広がって
Spreading,
咲いて
blooming,
駆け出して
running out,
飛んで
and flying!
だから JUST FLY TO THE STAR もっと WOW WOW
So, JUST FLY TO THE STAR! More WOW WOW!
世界中で PROUDY GLOW
PROUDY GLOW throughout the world!
存在など歌い切って無い無い
Sing until even existence itself is gone.
壊れても関係ない
Even if it breaks, it doesn't matter!
はーい！ということで...
Haaay! So with that...
新曲を披露させていただきました！
we got to perform our new song!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
ありがとうございました！かっこいい曲になりましたね、このみん！
Thank you so much! It turned out to be a really cool song, Konomin!
ええ曲！
Great song!
ということでですね、最強未来衝動...
And so, "Saikyou Mirai Shoudou"...
本日この後、7月2日0時からデジタルリリースされます！
will be released digitally today at midnight, July 2nd!
わーい！
Yay!
ちょっとせっかくなんで...
Since we have this chance...
この曲、実は...
this song, actually...
2人ね、2人で作詞を...
the two of us wrote the lyrics...
そうなんですよ
That's right.
いたしました！
we did!
2日間、一緒に缶詰状態になって...
We were cooped up together for two days...
一緒に缶詰になって、部屋に閉じこもって...
Cooped up together, locking ourselves in a room...
このみんと一緒に、あの、作詞をするという...
I wrote lyrics together with Konomin...
本当にね、内容盛りだくさんで...
There really was so much content.
そうだ、このね、新しい小悪魔衣装のこと、あんまり話せなかったので、
That's right! I couldn't talk much about this new little devil outfit,
この後、メン限でゆっくり見てもらえたらと思います。
so I hope you can take a closer look during the members-only stream after this.
実は、色んなアクセサリーや差分があります。ということで...
Actually, it has various accessories and variations. So,
ぜひメン限もよろしくお願いします！
please look forward to the members-only stream too!
そして、皆様！
And everyone!
最後にAZKiからみんなに、
lastly, from AZKi to all of you,
嬉しいお知らせです！
there is some exciting news!
こちらをどうぞ！
Please take a look!
傷ついた感情も連れていくから
Because I will carry even my hurt feelings with me
そっと響くファンファーレが新しい未来を感じてる
The softly echoing fanfare is sensing a new future
誇らしく歌って進むしかないでしょう
We have no choice but to sing proudly and move forward,
どこまでも
no matter how far.
届けこの祈りよ
Reach, this prayer of mine,
光となれ
and become the light!
もっと もっと
More, more,
少しずつでもいい
even if it's little by little,
優しいという答えを
give me the answer of kindness...
もっと
more,
more...
お待たせしました！
Thank you for waiting!
AZKiソロライブ2025「Departure」Blu-ray発売決定！
AZKi Solo Live 2025 "Departure" Blu-ray release confirmed!
開拓者のみんなと紡いだあのステージが何度でも見返せます！
You can rewatch that stage we created together with all the Pioneers as many times as you want!
本日から受注受付が開始です！
Orders are open starting today!
続いて、告知2つ目！
Next, the second announcement!
AZKiの歴史を彩るアルバム2作品の再販が、本日7月1日より全国流通スタート！
The re-release of the two albums that color AZKi's history starts national distribution today, July 1st!
対象タイトルは、『Without U』と『Re:Creating world』です！
The eligible titles are 'Without U' and 'Re:Creating world'!
最後、告知3つ目！
Lastly, the third announcement!
AZKi誕生日記念2026グッズ情報！
AZKi Birthday Celebration 2026 merchandise info!
今回は、お披露目された小悪魔衣装にちなんだグッズが盛りだくさんです！
This time, we have plenty of merchandise themed around the newly revealed little devil outfit!
イラストは、信澤収先生に描いていただきました！ありがとうございます！
The illustrations were drawn by Nobusawa Osamu-sensei! Thank you very much!
それでは詳細を見ていきましょう！
Now, let's take a look at the details!
まずは、こちら！
First, here is this!
2層アクリルパネル！
2-Layer Acrylic Panel!
小悪魔衣装のキービジュアルをアクリルパネルにしました！
The key visual of the little devil outfit is now an acrylic panel!
2層になっているので、立体的に見えます。
Since it's double-layered, it looks three-dimensional.
ステンドグラスの神秘的な美しさと小悪魔衣装が見せるギャップを楽しんでください！
Please enjoy the gap between the mysterious beauty of the stained glass and the little devil outfit!
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
ランダムラバーキーホルダー！
Random Rubber Keychain!
この後のメン限でも詳しく見せるんですけど、...
I'll show you more details in the members-only stream later, but
今回の新衣装、実はバリエーションがいっぱいあるので、ラバーキーホルダーにしてもらいました！...
this new outfit actually has many variations, so we made them into rubber keychains!
君のお気に入りはどのAZKiかな？
Which AZKi is your favorite?
イラストは、にゃとら先生に描いていただきました！
The illustrations were drawn by Nyatora-sensei!
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
ぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Plushie Keychain!
こちらも小悪魔衣装バージョンとなってます。
This is also the little devil outfit version.
使い魔みたいな茶目っ気のある表情になっているので、ぜひ相棒として連れ歩いてください！
It has a playful expression like a familiar, so please take it with you as your partner!
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
おそろいブレスレット！
Matching Bracelet!
小悪魔衣装をモチーフにしたデザインのブレスレットです。
This is a bracelet designed with the little devil outfit as a motif.
日常の中でさりげなく「推し」を身にまとえるのはもちろん、
Of course you can casually wear your favorite "oshi" in your daily life,
普段アクセサリーをつけない方には、新衣装の再現コレクションとしてもおすすめのグッズです。
and for those who don't usually wear accessories, it is also recommended as a replica collection of the new outfit.
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
ASMRボイス！
ASMR Voice!
ボイスタイトルは『小悪魔チャーミング』。
The voice title is "Little Devil Charming".
AZKiが小悪魔っぽく魔法をかけちゃう？そんな「もしも」のお話のASMRボイスです。...
AZKi casts a spell like a little devil? It's an ASMR voice about such a "what-if" story.
そして、フルセット購入特典もございます！
And there is also a full-set purchase bonus!
信澤収先生イラストのAZKiのタロット風カードと、
A tarot-style card of AZKi illustrated by Nobusawa Osamu-sensei,
特典ASMRボイスです！
and a bonus ASMR voice!
数量限定バージョンは、直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りです！
The limited edition version includes a hand-signed autograph and a foil-stamped printed message!
通常バージョンは、箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りです！
The regular version includes a foil-stamped printed autograph and message!
ということで、以上、嬉しいお知らせでした！
So, that's all for the exciting news!
この後はメン限でアンコールライブ！...
After this, we have the encore live in the members-only stream!
まだメン限に入っていない方も、まだ間に合うので、ぜひ入ってみてください！...
If you haven't joined membership yet, you're still in time, so please join us!
実は、今回の新衣装、...
Actually, for this new outfit,
みんなにまだ見せていない、あんな姿やこんな姿があるの、...
there are other styles and looks that I haven't shown everyone yet,
見に来てくれたら嬉しいです！...
so I'd be happy if you came to see them!
誕生日、たくさんお祝いしてくれて、ありがとう！...
Thank you so much for celebrating my birthday!
ライブも見てくれて、ありがとう！...
Thank you for watching the live stream too!
それじゃあ、この後、メン限で会おうね！...
Well then, see you in the members-only stream after this!
バイバーイ！...
Bye-bye!
AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover
平成対令和 アニソン歌合戦
Heisei vs. Reiwa Anisong Singing Battle
重大告知あり / 新衣装お披露目
Major Announcement Included / New Outfit Reveal